<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#style">
  <head>
    <layout/>
  </head>
  <body>
    <div xml:id="captions">
	  <p begin="00:00:00" end="00:00:03.5">Building Queensland Premier's Message</p>
    <p begin="00:00:04" end="00:00:08">Hi, and welcome to our Building Queensland website.</p>
    <p begin="00:00:08.5" end="00:00:16">This web site is a great way for you to find out what our record job-creating building program is delivering in your local community.</p>
    <p begin="00:00:16.5" end="00:00:23">Whether you are in Cape York, Cloncurry, or Currumbin, there's building happening right now, right across Queensland.</p>
    <p begin="00:00:23.5" end="00:00:31.5">We're building new hospitals and upgrading existing ones. We're building new roads, new police stations and better schools.</p>
    <p begin="00:00:31.5" end="00:00:40">We're working on projects that embrace Queensland's wonderful environment and lifestyle, with new children's playgrounds, and walking tracks and swimming pools.</p>
    <p begin="00:00:40" end="00:00:50">My Government is investing a record $18.2 billion on projects like these, in communities like yours – and more.</p>
    <p begin="00:00:50.5" end="00:01:00">It's more than any other State or Territory in Australia. It's securing 127,000 local jobs right across Queensland.</p>
    <p begin="00:01:00.5" end="00:01:06.5">Such a massive investment in building in these very difficult economic times was a big decision for the Government.</p>
    <p begin="00:01:07" end="00:01:10">But it's a decision I made my number one priority.</p>
	  <p begin="00:01:10.5" end="00:01:16">Why? Because it's creating jobs for Queenslanders, and it's building now what we need for tomorrow.</p>
	  <p begin="00:01:16.5" end="00:01:19.5">Behind every job is a working family.</p>
	  <p begin="00:01:20" end="00:01:26">There is a lot to love about Queensland. That's why 2,000 more people every week are calling Queensland home.</p>
	  <p begin="00:01:26.5" end="00:01:35">Our building program is building better schools, better hospitals, more roads, better public transport in communities just like yours.</p>
	  <p begin="00:01:36" end="00:01:45">It's about jobs for now. But it's also about training opportunities so that we can build and hang on to the skills that we will need in better times.</p>
	  <p begin="00:01:45.5" end="00:01:52">It's all about investing in jobs today and about building a stronger, better Queensland for the future. </p>
	  <p begin="00:01:52" end="00:01:55">Authorised by the Queensland Government 2009</p>
    </div>
  </body>
</tt>